now let's have a look at the pen tool as
现在让我们看一下钢笔工具，如下所示
an illustrator with the pen tool you can
使用钢笔工具的插图画家可以
create curved paths I outlined the
创建曲线路径，我概述了
letter d and made a screenshot of its
字母d并制作了其屏幕截图
nodes and handles I will recreate the
节点和句柄，我将重新创建
letter d with the pen tool as we can see
字母d和钢笔工具，如我们所见
the nodes of the large curves are placed
将放置大曲线的节点
at the outer edges of the curve and
在曲线的外边缘，
their handles are perfectly horizontal
它们的把手完全水平
or vertical
或垂直
to place the first point I click and
要放置我单击的第一个点并
hold down the mouse
按住鼠标
I now see a handle or arm that I can
我现在看到了我能看到的手柄或手臂
move around
四处走动
when I press Ctrl I can place the arm
当我按下Ctrl键时，我可以放置手臂
perfectly vertical
完全垂直
I will place the arm at the same height
我会把胳膊放在同样的高度
as in the example now I let go of the
与示例中一样，现在我放弃了
mouse in control
鼠标控制
then I click on the second point which
然后我点击第二点，
is the highest point of the curve I hold
是我所持曲线的最高点
down the mouse down again and press Ctrl
再次按下鼠标并按Ctrl键
now I drag the handle perfectly
现在我完美地拖动手柄
horizontal I will make the length of the
水平方向，我将使长度为
left arm fit the left example
左臂适合左手示例
the right arm needs to be shorter but I
右臂需要再短一些，但我
will do that at a later point I click on
稍后我会这样做，我点击
the third point and drag I don't have to
第三点和拖累我不一定要
press Ctrl because the arm doesn't have
按Ctrl键，因为手臂没有
to be horizontal I will match the left
为了保持水平，我将与左边相匹配
arm
手臂
now I will go up because I also have a
现在我要上去了，因为我还有一个
right arm I have a curve and not a
右臂我有一个曲线，而不是
straight line to get a straight line I
直线得到直线I
need to remove the right arm to remove
需要移除右臂才能移除
the right arm I press shift plus l i see
右臂我按Shift键加上L，我看到了
I now have a straight line because I
我现在有一条直线，因为我
need the line to go up vertically I
我需要这条线垂直向上
press Ctrl I click on the point above
按Ctrl键，然后单击上面的点
and still hold down control to also get
并且仍然按住控制也可以得到
a vertical arm I click on the next Point
我点击下一个点的垂直手臂
hold Ctrl and drag to match the right
按住Ctrl并拖动以匹配右侧
arm I have a sharp corner again so I
手臂我又有了锋利的拐角所以我
press shift plus l
按Shift+L
now we have a new situation I can't drag
现在我们有了一个我不能拖下去的新情况
on the Note above because that would
在上面的注释上，因为这将
give me a curve below so I hold Ctrl and
给我一条下面的曲线，这样我就可以按住Ctrl键并
click on the next point now I press
点击下一个点，现在我按下
enter to continue I click on the last
按Enter继续，我点击最后一个
point and hold down the mouse I drag out
指向并按住我拖出的鼠标
a single arm
一只胳膊
I click on the next Point drag and match
我点击下一个点拖拽和匹配
the left arm
左臂
to get a sharp corner I press shift L
为了得到一个尖锐的角球，我按下了Shift键L
again
再来一次
I hold Ctrl click on the next Point
按住Ctrl键单击下一个点
still hold Ctrl and drag out a vertical
仍然按住Ctrl键并拖出垂直
arm
手臂
I click press enter and drag out the
我单击并按Enter，然后拖出
left arm
左臂
I press shift L and click
我按住Shift键L并单击
I hold Ctrl and click on the point below
我按住Ctrl键并单击下面的点
at the corner I only need a left arm
在拐角处我只需要一只左臂
so I press enter and then drag the left
因此，我按下Enter键，然后拖动左侧
arm
手臂
I click and drag and press shift l i
我点击并拖动，然后按Shift键L I
hold Ctrl and click on the point above
按住Ctrl键并单击上面的点
then I click on the next point which
然后我点击下一个点，
also gives a straight line
也给出了一条直线
I press enter and drag an arm out then I
我按下Enter键并拖出一只手臂，然后我
click and hold Ctrl and match the left
单击并按住Ctrl并匹配左侧
arm
手臂
this is the second point where I will
这是第二点，我将
adjust the right arm later to finish the
稍后调整右臂以完成
path I click on the first Point again
路径我再次点击第一个点
hold Ctrl and match the bottom arm
按住Ctrl键并匹配下臂
now I click on the Node tool I will
现在我单击节点工具，我将
adjust the two right arms that are too
调整两只右臂，也就是
long I click on the note on top and hold
我长时间点击顶部的音符，然后按住
my mouse above the right arm I hold Ctrl
鼠标位于右臂上方，按住Ctrl键
and drag the arm to match I do the same
然后拖着手臂来匹配我也是这样做的
for the bottom note I click on it hold
对于底部的音符，我点击它，按住
Ctrl and drag the right arm in the outer
按住Ctrl键并在外部拖动右臂
path is now finished
路径现在已完成
now I draw the Inner Path I click on the
现在，我绘制内部路径，然后单击
pen tool I click hold Ctrl and drag then
钢笔工具我点击按住Ctrl键并拖动
I click hold Ctrl and drag again as
我单击按住Ctrl键并再次拖动为
before I will adjust the right arm later
在我稍后调整右臂之前
I click and drag to get a corner I press
我点击并拖动以获得我按下的角
shift L again
L再次移位
I hold Ctrl and click I press enter and
按住Ctrl键并单击，然后按Enter键
drag an arm then I click hold Ctrl and
拖动手臂，然后单击按住Ctrl键
drag and to finish I click hold Ctrl and
拖动并按下按住Ctrl键完成操作
drag
拖曳
like before I adjust the top and bottom
就像之前我调整顶部和底部
arms I click on the note on top and hold
手臂，我点击上面的音符，然后按住
my mouse above the right arm
我的鼠标在右臂上方
I hold Ctrl and drag the arm to match I
我按住Ctrl键并拖动手臂以匹配I
do the same for the bottom node I click
对我单击的底部节点执行相同的操作
on it hold Ctrl and drag the right arm
在其上按住Ctrl键并拖动右臂
in the Inner Path is now finished now I
在内在路径中现在完成了现在我
have to make the paths a compound path I
必须使路径成为一条复合路径
select them both and go to path
将它们都选中并转到路径
difference I will make the trace Letter
不同的是我会做追踪信
Black in the next lecture we will have a
黑色在下一节课中我们将有一个
closer look at the node tool
仔细观察节点工具